[{"answer": "I think you always have to worry about North Korea.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Is there a particular threat because we have a new young certainly unpredictable leader there, or is it just the same old stuff?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, it's always the wild card.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "I mean, what happens then?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, I think, first of all, Robin hit it exactly right.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Is the onus really on China rather than America to control what's going on?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Well, look, let's take the examples, and I hate to disappoint you, but let's take the examples of the recent cases.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Am I wrong here?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Look, I think it depends what you mean by universal.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "So are you against universal background checks?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "First of all, under the current gun check system, we know that 70,000 convicted felons have tried to buy a gun.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Why would any rational person not want to know who is selling guns to who?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "But when you sell a car --", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "The question I'd raise for you is you think any of the kids in South Side Chicago who are parts of teenaged gangs are going to go out and go through a gun check?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "When you sell a car, Newt -- when you sell a car, you have to register it, you have to know who has sold it and to who.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "What are you trying to accomplish?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "I mean, what does that mean?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Because I want to know -- I want to know if you're a criminal, I want to know if you're mentally sound.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Sorry if again I sound naive but why the hell wouldn't I want to know that?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "The greatest gun salesman in American history is President Barack Obama.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Well, I can assure you I'm going to read their reasoning and I'm going to try to understand why they took that position.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Do you agree with the Catholic bishops?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "You know, I think we could have a wonderful evening and we'll talk and we'll compare notes on your position on right to life and my position on guns, and maybe during the course of the evening, we could have a Catholic to Catholic come-together and decide exactly how much each of us could support the bishops.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Do you agree with your own bishops?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Well, it's very sad to hear of his passing, although he and others, myself included, knew that it was -- it was going to happen at some point.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "What was your reaction to the great Roger Ebert?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "He either gave you a thumbs up or gloriously if you were a real triumph, two thumbs up, or a thumbs down and it could make or break a movie, couldn't it?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "How should we remember Roger?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "I think that Roger would like to be remembered as a real communicator about the power of movies to give people really insights into themselves.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "How would he like to be remembered?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "How should we remember Roger Ebert and what advice do you think you should give to other film critics who may be coming up on the blocks as to how they should do this quite unique job that he did?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Yes, I bumped into him a couple of times.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "I guess you two probably came across him a few times, right?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Well, I tell you, one time I was in a green room going on to Oprah Winfrey with, like, Universal executives in the green room, Ronnie Howard, Brian Grazer, Kurt Russell, Robert De Niro, and they all got up when he walked in the room, and they all sort of milling around him, and like making sure he was OK.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "What effect did it have on actors?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I think it's an overstatement about it bifurcating the party, Piers, because actually I prefer to be in a party where diversity viewpoints on these issues are welcome rather than the party that seems to have this litmus test that you must feel a certain way.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "How do you come together in time for the next election in 2016 with any kind of united front when these social issues appear to be ripping the party in two?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "They don't get it.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Why can't they be married?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "He -- Piers, he could have been stopped.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Kellyanne?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "James Holmes could have been stopped had the police listened to his therapist who had actual knowledge --", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "How would you stop him?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "The vast majority of people who have mental illness problems never hurt anybody.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "How much more does somebody have to do before America goes no, we're going to stop these people getting such easy access to this kind of fire power?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "A tiny --", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "What do you call tiny numbers?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Do you know how many have been killed by guns since Sandy Hook?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Every time you make this argument, every time you make it, the -- what you do is you start with the mass murderers, and then you will ask how many gun shootings there are.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Haven't you?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Well, you're not talking about whether they should be regulated or not.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Why shouldn't guns be regulated exactly the same way as cars, alcohol, tobacco?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Do you believe those will be stopped by background checks?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Yes -- well, I support true background checks that allow us to know who has the gun, meaning without registering them because that doesn't work.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Kellyanne, do any of the proposals that you've heard about controlling gun violence in America, do you support anything that would actually reduce the number of guns in circulation?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "Well, this is why we're having this debate.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130404pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "Do you need that to protect your home and your family and your land?", "qSentId": 641}]